EXPERIENCE

FreeCodeCampBCN coding meetup co-organizer

Worked developing solutions for the online business of Antiquari&Vintage, which involved organizing their data, creating simple web tools and social presence

later Matiz by 20thDesign

Jazz piano player and composer in different scenarios in Colombia and Germany

Bartman and waiter

SKILLSET

Dic 2017 now

2015 - 2016

2012 - 2015

2010 - 2012

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript

VueJS

 $\star\star\star\star$ NodeJS

Express $\star \star \star \diamond \diamond \diamond$ SASS MongoDB Mongoose

 $\star\star\star\star\star$ German, English Spanish

> $\Rightarrow \Rightarrow \Diamond$ French

★☆☆ Catalan

Nicolas Ramirez

Git

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

When I arrived to Germany, in little more than one year I had my german language certification and got accepted in the UdK Berlin for Composition. This same mindset drives me now to acomplish my goals in programming and web development.

I am tenacious, and insightful when it comes to learning. I love and breath for it! I am always ready to engage new and challenging concepts and ideas..

I am eager to work in your team!

Codecademy - Khanacademy

EDUCATION

HTML5 & CSS3

FreeCodeCamp

80% Frontend Curriculum 70% Backend Curriculum

Udemv

Andrew Mead's "The Complete Node.js Developer Course" Colt Steele "The Web Developer Bootcamp"

> Assisting different jazz workshops and music related seminars while working as a musician.

Composition Student in UdK Berlin - Music Bachelor

Conservatory SVA Composition (University Music Preparation)

Highschool

INTEREST

- Music composition/ production/ software
- Science Fiction Novels and literature in general like Haruki Murakami.
- Meditation, Yoga, Martial Arts. I used to practice some Kung Fu a while ago

2013 - 2015

PROJECT

LINKS

Portafolio

nikameush.com

github.com/kamatheuska

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/nikameush

segersian.github.io/freecodecampbcn

2016 - 2017

2011 - 2012

2009 - 2011

2007